<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Easter with Christ</string>
    <string name="app_name">Live with Christ</string> 
    <string name="titlePrefs">Settings</string> 
    <string name="prefsMenuTitle">Settings</string> 
	<string name="menuRestartWeek">Restart week</string>
    <string name="titleViewBibleTextActivity">Bible text</string> 
    <string name="titleEaster">Easter with Jesus</string> 
    <string name="reklmatext1"><a href="http://www.hcjb.org/">HCJB Global</a></string> 
    <string name="reklmatext2"><a href="http://www.hcjb.org/">HCJB Global</a></string> 
    <string name="reklmatext3"><a href="http://www.hcjb.org/">HCJB Global</a></string> 
    <string name="reklmatext4"><a href="http://www.hcjb.org/">HCJB Global</a></string> 
    <string name="reklmatext5"><a href="http://www.hcjb.org/">HCJB Global</a></string> 
    <string name="bibleSource">\n\n - Svenska Folkbibeln</string> 
    <string name="bibleSourceNET">\n\n - NET Bible®</string> 
    <string name="start_easter_button">Activate Easter Week</string> 
    <string name="continue_easter_button">Read Bible Texts</string> 
    <string name="read_again_easter_button">Read Texts Again</string> 
    <string name="about_hcjb_button">About HJCB</string> 
    <string name="instructions_button">Instructions</string> 
    <string name="hcjb_activity_header">About HCJB Global Sweden</string> 
    <string name="hcjb_activity_text">HCJB Global Sweden is an organization spreading the word about Jesus Christ.
      The organization is a part of HCJB Global. 
      \nRead more about <a href="http://www.hcjb.se">HCJB Global Sweden</a>(Swedish only)
      \nRead more about <a href="http://www.hcjb.org">HCJB Global</a></string>
	<string name="about_header">About the Application</string>
	<string name="about_text">This application is a completely new way to read the Bible, created by HCJB Global Sweden.
	  \n\nWhen Easter Week is started (either manually by setting a date, or waiting for the real Easter week to begins), 
	  you will follow Christ in real time from when he enters Jerusalem until he meets his followers after the resurrection.
	  Bible texts from all four gospels are notified during the days (and nights!) until Easter Day. 
	  Please expect that you have to spend some time together with this application to follow Christ this week; More
	  than one hundred bible texts will be notified and displayed!
	  \n\nOnce all the bible texts are read, additional features are unlocked on the start screen.
	  \n\nThis application has been made to bring the suffering and sacrifice of Christ to mind during Easter week.
	  \n\nThe background image is a painting by Diego Velázquez, available as Public Domain picture from Wikipedia.
	  \n\nThe origin of the background photo (empty tomb) is unknown.
	  \n\nBible texts are from Svenska Folkbibeln (Swedish) and the NET Bible (English).
	  \n\nScripture quoted by permission. All scripture quotations, unless otherwise indicated, are
	  taken from the NET Bible® copyright ©1996-2006 by Biblical Studies Press, L.L.C.
	  www.bible.org All rights reserved. This material is available in its entirety as a free
	  download or online web use at http://netbible.org/ .
	  \n\nSvenska Folkbibeln, Copyright (C) 1996, 1998, Stiftelsen Svenska Folkbibeln, Stockholm, 
	  and Stiftelsen Biblicum, Ljungby.
	  </string>
	<string name="help_header">Help on the application</string>
	<string name="help_text">Start easter week by clicking on the "Read Bible Texts" button. Follow Christ the last week before his death and resurrection. Additional features will be unlocked when all texts are read.</string>
	<string name="about_app_button">About the app</string>
	<string name="started_header">Application has started</string>
	<string name="started_text">Application has started, but no text has been displayed yet. Please be patient and wait for the first text to come, it will be notified: </string>
	<string name="started_today">Today!</string>
	<string name="started_tomorrow">Tomorrow!</string>
	<string name="started_number_days1">in</string>
	<string name="started_number_days2">days...</string>
	<string name="set_date_header">Set date...</string>
	<string name="set_date_text">Please set the date for Easter day; preferably next coming Sunday.
		\nThe first text will be displayed one week before the selected date.
		\n\nEaster day date:</string>
	<string name="set_date_button_next">Start easter week!</string>
	<string name="start_next_step">Next step</string>
	<string name="start_feedback">Feedback</string>
	<string name="start_header">Easter Application</string>
	<string name="start_find_church">Find a church</string>
	<string name="start_give_button">Support HCJB</string>
	<string name="next_step_header">Next step...</string>
	<string name="next_step_text">Now, you have lived one week together with Christ. Do you want to follow Christ for the rest of your life?
	  \n\nThe Bible tells us that "if you confess with your mouth that Jesus is Lord and believe in your heart that God raised him from the dead, you will be saved. " (Rom. 10:9)
	  \n\nThat is all you need to do to be saved! Press the buttons below for assistance in the three steps: 
	  \n1. Pray the salvation prayer! 
	  \n2. Find a church, and tell others about your faith! 
	  \n3. Share with us that you have received Christ!</string>
	<string name="find_church_header">Find a church near you!</string>
	<string name="find_church_text">Please contact HCJB Global if you need assistance in finding a church: <a href="mailto:info@hcjb.org">info@hcjb.org</a></string>
	<string name="feedback_header">Send Feedback!</string>
	<string name="feedback_text">Tell us at HCJB Global Sweden if this application has been helpful for you in your relation to Christ.\n
		\n<a href="mailto:android@hcjb.se?Subject=Android+app+feedback">Send Feedback!</a></string>
	<string name="alert_last_text_ok">OK!</string>
	<string name="alert_last_text_text">All texts are now read. New functions have been enabled on the start page.</string>
	<string name="next_step_btn_pray">Pray the salvation prayer</string>
	<string name="next_step_btn_find_church">Find a church!</string>
	<string name="next_step_btn_feedback">Send feedback to HCJB!</string>
	<string name="next_step_salvation_prayer">Pray out, loud, your own prayer for salvation. The words are not the important thing,
					what is important is your hearts desire to give your life to Jesus. If you do not know what to
					pray, the following can serve as a prayer;
					\n\nDear Lord, I admit that I am a sinner. I have done many things that don’t please you.
					I have lived my life for myself. I am sorry and I repent. I ask you to forgive me.
					I believe that you died on the cross for me, to save me. You did what I could not do for myself.
					I come to you now and ask you to take control of my life, I give it to you.
					Help me to live every day in a way that pleases you. I love you, Lord, and I thank you that I will
					spend all eternity with you. \n\nAmen. </string>
	<string name="next_step_popup_ok">OK!</string>
	<string name="weekday_monday">Monday</string>
	<string name="weekday_tuesday">Tuesday</string>
	<string name="weekday_wednesday">Wednesday</string>
	<string name="weekday_thursday">Thursday</string>
	<string name="weekday_friday">Friday</string>
	<string name="weekday_saturday">Saturday</string>
	<string name="weekday_sunday">Sunday</string>
	<string name="change_the_date_btn">Change the date</string>
	<string name="bibleTranslationShortNET">NET</string>
	<string name="bibleTranslationShortSFB">SFB</string>
	<string name="select_bible_translation">Select which Bible translation to be used
	\nNew English Translation - NET
	\Svenska Folkbibeln - SFB</string>
	<string name="prefsEnableInsistentModeTitle">Insistent Mode</string>
	<string name="enableInsistentModeSummary">Do not leave your device if enabled! Beep will drain battery and your friends!</string>
	<string name="selectBibleTranslationTitle">Select bible translation</string>
	<string name="selectBibleTranslationSummary">Which bible translation (and language) that should be used for the bible texts.</string>
	<string name="wrongDateText">The date for Easter day must be minimum 5 days in future!</string>
	<string name="selectAlertTitle">Select alert type</string>
	<string name="selectAlertSummary">How much the alert for a new text to read should sound.</string>
	<string name="toastTextNoReset">Easter week can not be reset when close to real Easter week.</string>
	<string name="confirmRestartWeek">Are you sure you want to restart Easter Week?</string>
	<string name="confirmRestartWeekYes">Yes</string>
	<string name="confirmRestartWeekNo">No</string>
</resources>
